alright guys welcome back to another tutorial and in this video finally going
好吧欢迎回到 另一个人 教程，在 这个视频 终于去了
to start talking to you about classes and objects and some cool things that
开始和 你谈论课程 和对象 以及一些很酷的东西
you can do with them so first of all what the heck is a class well the most
你首先 可以做到这一点 什么是最好的课程
simple definition is basically a class is an easy way where you can group
简单定义基本上是一个类 是一种可以分组的简单方法
similar variables and functions together so say you're making a computer game
类似的变量 和功能在一起 所以说，你正在做 一个 电脑游戏
usually all of the functions dealing with enemies and all the variables through you would want in an enemy class
通常所有 的功能 都 在 处理 与敌人和所有变量 通过你想要的敌人类
maybe you have a different one for moving your character around well all of
也许你有一个不同 的 四处 移动你的性格 以及所有的
those functions for moving your main character would be in a character class so on and so forth so again the most
那些移动你的主要功能 字符将在字符类中 等等，等等 如此反复 的最
simple definition is it's a really cool way we can group similar variables and
简单的定义是非常酷的 我们可以将类似变量分组的方式
functions together might be in record okay just check in so with that being
功能可能在一起记录 好吧，只需 检查即可
said let's go ahead and look at an example right now so in order to make a class type the keyword class and then at
说让我们继续看看 现在的例子，以便制作一个 class键入关键字class然后在
his face now class pretty much says hey Python I'm about to make a class now
现在他的脸 几乎说嘿 Python我现在要上课了
after this what you want to do is you want to name your class something and
在此之后你想做的就是你 希望把你的东西类和
it's common practice to name it with a capital letter and this is just so programmers can differentiate between a
这是常见的做法是 用它命名 大写字母 就是这样 程序员可以区分 a
class and like a normal variable or a function or anything like that so this
类和正常变量或类似 功能或类似的东西 所以这个
is how we make a class called enemy now add a colon now whatever is indented
就是我们现在如何创建一个叫做敌人的类 现在添加一个冒号， 无论是缩进的
after this is going to be part of your enemy class so every variable inside
在此之后将成为你的一部分 敌人类里面的每一个变量
here and every function is going to belong to this enemy class so let's go
这里和每个功能都会发生 属于这个敌人阶级所以我们走了
ahead and make a simple variable first so we'll say that each enemy has a life
提前做一个 简单的变量 所以我们会说每个 敌人都有生命
of 3 so now this life variable is actually part of this enemy class just
3 所以现在这种生活变量 实际上只是这个敌人阶级的一部分
remember that so now what we can do is we can make a couple functions for this
记住，现在我们能做的就是 我们可以为此做一些功能
class so what's one thing that we can do we'll say we'll make a function called
所以 我们可以做 的一 件事是什么 我们会说我们会 调用一个函数
attack and this is just some what happens whenever we attack an enemy now
攻击，这只是一些什么 当我们现在攻击一个敌人时就会发生
check this out whenever I'm just writing these parentheses right here
我只是在写作的时候看看这个 这些括号就在这里
what PyCharm did is automatically filled in this keyword of self now this is going to be a little confusing until I
PyCharm所做的是 自动填充的 在这个关键字的自我现在 这是 在我 之前会有点困惑
finish this program and explain what objects are but pretty much think of
完成这个程序并解释一下 对象几乎可以想到
whenever you see self it means use something from this own class so if you
每当你看到自我，就意味着使用 来自这个班级的东西， 所以如果你
say you're going to see later like self attack it means use the attack function
说你以后会像自我一样看到 攻击它意味着使用攻击功能
in this class self life means use the life variable in this class again kind
在这一课堂上，自我生活意味着使用 这个班的生活变量再次 类型
of confusing at first but you guys are going to see later on what it does
起初令人困惑，但你们是 稍后会看到 它的作用
alright so let's make this function actually do something whenever we attack
好的 ，让我们做这个 功能 实际上每当我们攻击时都会做
the anime we'll just do something like print attack or actually let's print
动画我们就这样做 打印攻击或 实际让我们打印
ouch we'll say that at the end we says ouch
哎哟 我们会说最后我们说哎哟
and also what we want to do is we want to subtract one from the enemy's life
我们想做的也是我们想做的 从 敌人的生命中减去一个
now we can't just do this check it out if we just try to subtract one from life
现在我们不能这样做检查出来 如果我们只是试图从生活中减去一个
we get a little error what we actually need to do is what I was talking about
我们实际上得到了一点错误 需要 做的是什么，我说的是
put self life so that's how you access the variables inside your class so
把自己的生命放在这里就是你的访问方式 你班里的变量是这样的
pretty much self is saying okay inside this class take away one from the life
几乎是自我在里面说好 这堂课从生活中夺走了一个人
variable simple enough maybe it was easy I don't understand who knew all right so
变量很简单也许很容易 我不明白谁知道这一切
let's make one more function so this class isn't that boring I'll make
让我们再做一个 功能吧 上课不是那么无聊 我会做的
another function to check the enemy's life and of course it automatically
另一个检查 敌人的功能 生活当然是自动的
fills in that self variable and we'll say I don't know maybe a little if
填写 自变量 ，我们将 说我 不知道，也许一点点 如果
statement so if self not slough so if self life is less than or equal to zero and this is actually another thing I
声明如果自己没有蜕皮那么如果 自我生命小于或等于零 这实际上是另一 件事我
want to point out whenever you're making computer games don't just check if the enemy's life is equal to zero to see if
想要在你制作时指出 电脑游戏不只是检查是否 敌人的生命等于零，看看是否
they're dead because like if they had three life and you had like a super
他们已经死了， 因为他们已经死了 三个生命，你就像一个超级
powerful weapon to like slash them in and took away five life well then their
喜欢削减他们的强大武器 并带走了五个生命 然后他们的
life would be negative two so always make sure to check if it's less than or
生活将是负面的， 所以总是如此 确保 检查它是否小于或
equal to zero just a little I don't know tip for game development so if they're
等于零 ，只是一 点点，我不 知道 游戏开发的提示，如果他们是
less than or equal to we'll just print something like I am
小于或等于 我们只会 打印像我一样的东西
dead Bob the enemy obviously couldn't say anything if it was dead but this is
死鲍勃的敌人显然不能 说什么， 如果它已经死了，但这是
our game we could do what do you want alright so if they're dead they're dead
我们的游戏我们可以 做你想要的 好吧，如果他们死了，他们就死定了
else we'll just print out like how much life they had lab so print something
否则 我们只会打印 出多少 生活 他们有实验室所以打印的东西
like of course we need to convert it to a string so print out the amount of life
像 我们当然需要将 其 转换 为 一个字符串，所以打印出生命的数量
that they have left and we'll just do something like this life left like -
他们离开了，我们会做的 像这样的 生活就像 -
life left one life left tomato tomahto alright so right now we have a very simple class of enemy so the
生命离开了一个人生 番茄tomahto 好吧， 现在我们 有一个 非常简单的敌人类所以
enemy has three life and we can attack him whenever we call this function it takes one life away and also anytime we
敌人有三个生命，我们可以攻击 每当我们称之为这个功能时他 需要一个卖身契，也随时 都
can have it check to see how much life the enemy has if it's dead it prints out
可以检查看看有多少生命 如果敌人已经死了，它会被打印掉
I'm dead or if it's not that it tells you how much life you guys love simple
我死了， 或者它不是它告诉我的 你们多么 喜欢简单的 生活
enough now if we just try to do something like this attack okay well that's not working now the reason that
如果我们只是尝试做 ，现在就足够了 像这样的攻击很好 现在 这 不起作用 的原因
this doesn't work is because in order to use anything inside your class you need
这不起作用是 因为为了 在课堂上使用你需要的 任何东西
to access it a special way and that is by creating something called an object
以 一种特殊的 方式 访问 它 ，就是这样 通过创建一个称为对象的东西
now an object just think of it like this it's pretty much a way that you can
现在的目标只是 觉得它 像这样 这几乎 是你的方式
access the stuff inside your class and I know I just say that twice but it's
访问 你班级里面 的东西 和我 知道我只是说 两次，但它是
actually really important to understand and they're really easy to make as well
理解其实非常重要 他们真的很容易做 ，以及
so the first thing you do is you pretty much act like you're making a normal
所以你要做的第一件事就是漂亮 很像你正在做 正常的 事情
variable so I'm going to make a object called enemy one so what you said it
变量所以我要做一个对象 所谓的敌人就是你所说的
equal to is the class that you want to use stuff from so I want to use the
等于 你想要 的班级 使用的东西所以我想使用
stuff inside the enemy class so anytime I want to use that I need this object
什么时候在 敌人类 里面 的东西 我想用 我 需要这个对象
code enemy 1 and it's object from this class right here so now we can just do
代码敌人 1和 它的对象 在这里上课，所以现在我们可以 做
something called enemy one
一种叫做敌人的东西
attack and what this pretty much means is this it says okay enemy one is an
攻击以及这几乎意味着什么 是这样它说好的敌人 是一个
object from what class while enemy so go to the class enemy and once you're in
敌人如此前往 什么阶级的对象 对于阶级敌人，一旦你进入
there use attack so now if we try to run this it would say ouch because it just took one away from the enemy and
如果 我们试图运行 ，现在使用攻击 这会说哎呀因为它 只是 从 敌人 那里拿走了一个
actually if we check life to make sure that worked whenever we run this said
实际上，如果我们检查生活，以确保 只要我们运行这个就行了
okay it starts with three of course so we're going to attack this enemy once
好吧，它 当然是以三个 开头的 我们要攻击这个敌人一次
say ouch then it says two life left now I want to
说哎哟 然后它说现在我想要 两个生命
show you guys one other really cool thing and this is probably the main
告诉你们其他人真的很酷 事情， 这可能是 主要的
reason that people use classes all the time see each object is actually a copy
原因是 人们使用类所有 时间看每个对象 实际上是一个副本
of its class so each object is actually independent of one another
它的类， 所以每个对象实际上 相互独立
so check this out don't understand what I mean you will in just a second say
所以看看这个 不明白什么 我的意思是你会在 一秒钟之内说出来
that we have enemy one instead we have another enemy called enemy to actually let me code this entire thing and then
我们有敌人， 而不是我们有 另一个敌人 实际上 叫 敌人 让我编写这整个事情然后
I'll talk you guys through do this
我会告诉你们这些人
alright so what's going to happen is we're going to make two objects or two
好吧那 会 发生 什么 事 我们要做两个或两个对象
copies from this class one of them is going to be stored in the object enemy
从这个班级复制其中一个 是 将 被存储在对象 的敌人
one and another one is going to be stored in the object enemy two now each
一个，另一个将 是 现在每个存储在敌人两个对象中
of these are pretty much thinking though think of them like their own enemies so
其中几乎是在 思考 想起他们 喜欢自己的敌人 等等
each of those has three life each so whenever you attack enemy one it doesn't
每个人都有三个生命 每当你攻击敌人时，它就不会
affect enemy two so let me run this and I'll show you guys what I'm talking
影响敌人二，所以让我跑吧 我会告诉你们我在说什么
about so we created two objects we attacked and me one twice and then check
为此我们创建了两个对象 攻击我和我两次，然后检查
this life and it had one life left however enemy two is still had three
这一生， 它还有一个生命 然而敌人两人仍然有三个
life left so this is how people make computer games
生命离开了，这就是 人们的生活方式 电脑游戏
with one class which is pretty much a template of how do you want to code the
有一个类，几乎是一个 你想 怎么 编码的模板
enemy how do you want it to act and behave and you can create as many of
敌人你想如何行动和 表现得很好，你可以创造尽可能多的
them as you want just by making an object for each one so how awesome is that
他们只是想制作 一个 每个 人 都有 一个 对象，那 真是太棒了 那
so that is the basics of a class pretty much not only a group of similar
所以这是一个漂亮的课程的基础 不仅是一群 相似的人
functions and objects but pretty much a template of how you want an object to
功能和对象，但几乎是一个 你怎么想 的对象模板
behave and act and of course you can make as many copies of it as you want
表现和行为，当然你可以 让你 想 它 的多个副本
and each of the objects are independent of one another so if you guys don't
并且每个对象都是独立的 彼此 所以，如果你们 没有 的
completely understand this or it seems kind of like unfamiliar whenever we
完全理解这个或似乎 我们什么时候都有点陌生
start making other programs is going to become second nature and also really
开始做其他程序 将要 成为第二天性而且真的
easy to understand but that is the basics of classes and objects in Python
容易理解，但那是 Python中类和对象的基础知识
and also if you have any questions then ask me on my forum but for now thank you
如果您有任何问题，也可以 在我的论坛上问我， 但现在谢谢你
guys for watching don't forget subscribe and I'll see you next tutorial
观看的人不要忘记订阅 我会 在下一个 教程中 看到你